

CONTACT ME AT

- Bangalow No A-8- SEC 36 GUL HOUSE Near Safoora chowrangi Gulistan e Juhar Block 7
- ► HATESHKUMAR701@GMAIL.COM
- +92-3313612701

SKILLS SUMMARY

ANDROID (JAVA/KOTLIN)
DEVELOPMENT

FLUTTER DEVELOPMENT

IOS (SWIFT) DEVELOPMENT

JAVA (J2SE/J2EE)

MYSQL/SQL/SQLITE/FIREBASE /YQL/POSTGRESQL/

ROOM/REALM/FIREBASE/JDBC

WEBRTC/TWILLIO/OPEENTOK (VIDEO CALLING)

TRACK/ANALYSIS/WEBENGGAGED/ADJUST

RXJAVA/RXDART/

CA/MVVM.MVC/MVP

DAGGER/DAGGER HILT

C/C++/OOP

HATESH KUMAR

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Senior Mobile Developer specializing in Flutter
Development, Android Native development. Experienced
with all stages of the development cycle for mobile projects.
Well-versed in numerous programming languages including
Dart, Java, Swift OOP, PHP, Kotlin, MySQL. Strong
background in moblie development and Web API
development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR MOBILE APP DEVELOPER May 2018 - Ongoing

• EPLANET COMMUNCATION INC PAKISTAN

ANDROID DEVELOPER April 2017 - April 2018

UHF SOLUTIONS PAKISTAN

TRAINEE ANDROID DEVELOPER November 2016 - January 2017

• INTELLISENSE SOLUTIONS PAKISTAN

TRAINEE ANDROID DEVELOPER May 2016 - August 2016

MINDSCAPE TECHNOLOGIES PAKISTAN

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

HAMDARD UNIVERSITY KARACHI

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING | April 20013 - January 2017

 Computer System Engineering - Software Development Track

MINDSCAPE TECHNOLOGIES

ANDROID TRAINING | March 2016 - May 2016

FLUTTER PROJECTS

- Dietbox App
- Match N Stick
- OK Click n Collect App
- Fitness Food App
- · Who's Up?! App
- MIP Android App
- Bilty App
- SnapEx App

ANDROID NATIVE PROJECTS

- RFID based student attendance system Android App and Desktop App with hardware integration(FYP)
- GOTO.com.pk App
- Helpp App
- Radio 2Go
- Talentview App
- Shifaam HealthApp Your Healthcare Companion
- Shifaam Doctor App
- SteathOwl VPN App
- 2Click Client
- 2Click Partner
- Meezan Bank Sales Force App
- Atlas Honda App
- CoinExchange App
- SteathOwl VPN App